https://legal.majestri.com.au/privacy-policy?v=1.0

Majestri Pty Ltd30 Glen Road, The Gap QLD 4061Andrew Holman 0437 238 778
Privacy Policy
Version 1.0 LS00-1MatterDescriptionThis is Majestri Pty Ltd’s privacy policy dated 14th of September 2017 (“Privacy Policy”) LS00-3NumberedParaThis Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your information, including any Personal Information.
It applies to the Majestri Website, which is available at https://majestri.com.au, and all sub-domains, related sites, applications, services and tools regardless of how you access them (“Majestri Website”). LS00-3NumberedParaThis Privacy Policy is available at https://legal.majestri.com.au/privacy-policy. LS00-3NumberedParaDefinitions and Interpretation LS00-99H2In this Privacy Policy, each of the following terms has the corresponding meaning: LS00-3NumberedPara“Personal Information” means information or an opinion about an identified individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable: LS00-4SubParaAlphawhether the information or opinion is true or not; and LS00-5SubParaRomanwhether the information or opinion is recorded in a material form or not. LS00-5SubParaRoman “User” or “you” means any user of the Majestri Website including without limitation any person that: LS00-4SubParaAlphaViews the Majestri Website in a browser;
LS00-5SubParaRomanSubmits any information to the Majestri Website, through use of an enquiry form, or otherwise. LS00-5SubParaRomanParties bound LS00-99H2By accessing the Majestri Website, or by submitting any information to us, you accept this Privacy Policy.
LS00-3NumberedParaWe may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on the Majestri Website.
It is your responsibility to review the information provided in this Privacy Policy, and to determine if it is suitable for your purposes.
LS00-3NumberedParaMajestri Pty Ltd is not currently bound to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles, and nothing in this policy shall be read to impose any obligation beyond that set out in this Privacy Policy. LS00-3NumberedParaHow we collect information LS00-99H2We collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone, or other access device when you: LS00-3NumberedParaNavigate to the Majestri Website, or any related pages with web browser; or LS00-4SubParaAlphaSubmit any information using an enquiry form or by any other method provided on the Majestri Website. LS00-4SubParaAlphaInformation that we collect LS00-99H2The information sent to us includes data on the pages you access, device identifiers, your location, standard web log data, and other information.
LS00-3NumberedParaWeb log data incudes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from the Majestri Website.
LS00-3NumberedParaIn order to help protect you from fraud and misuse of your Personal Information, we may collect information about your use and interaction with the Majestri Website. For example, we may evaluate your computer, mobile phone or other access device to identify any malicious software or activity. LS00-3NumberedParaWe may also collect additional information from or about you in other ways, such as through results when you respond to a survey or poll, and from interactions with any other person through the Majestri Website. LS00-3NumberedParaHow we use Cookies LS00-99H2When you access the Majestri Website, we (including companies we work with) may place small data files on your computer, or other device. These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications (collectively “Cookies”).
We use Cookies to: LS00-3NumberedParaIdentify you; LS00-4SubParaAlphaEnable functionality on and to customise the Majestri Website and related content; LS00-4SubParaAlphaMeasure promotional effectiveness; and LS00-4SubParaAlphaMitigate risk and prevent fraud.. LS00-4SubParaAlphaWe use both session and persistent Cookies.
Session Cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your Account or close your browser.
Persistent Cookies remain on your browser until you erase them or they expire. LS00-3NumberedParaWe encode our Cookies so that we can interpret the information stored in them.
You are free to decline our Cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of the Majestri Website.
LS00-3NumberedParaYou may encounter Cookies on websites that we do not control.
For example, if you access a third party website from the Majestri Website, there may be a Cookie placed by the web page or an application within it. LS00-3NumberedParaHow we protect and store Personal Information LS00-99H2Throughout this Privacy Policy, we use the term “Personal Information” to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been made anonymous and does not identify a specific User.
LS00-3NumberedParaWe store and process your Personal Information on our computers in New South Wales, and Queensland, Australia. We protect your information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure and alteration. LS00-3NumberedParaHow we use the Personal Information we collect LS00-99H2Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customised experience.
We may use your Personal Information to: LS00-3NumberedParaProvide the Majestri Website, our services, and customer support; LS00-4SubParaAlphaResolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; LS00-4SubParaAlphaPrevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions, which can be viewed at https://legal.majestri.com.au/website-terms-and-conditions; LS00-4SubParaAlphaCustomise, measure, and improve the Majestri Website; LS00-4SubParaAlphaDeliver targeted marketing, Service update notices, and promotional offers to you; LS00-4SubParaAlphaContact you at any telephone number, by placing a voice call or through text (SMS), or email messaging, as authorised by our Terms and Conditions; or LS00-4SubParaAlphaCompare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. LS00-4SubParaAlphaMarketing LS00-99H2We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalise the Majestri Website, content, and advertising.
If you do not wish to receive marketing communication with us, outside of the Majestri Website then you may opt-out at any time by using the unsubscribe or opt-out feature contained in the communication that we send to you. LS00-3NumberedParaInformation generated by the Majestri Website, which includes data relating to your use of the Majestri Website, is used by us for our internal development purposes; such information does not contain any Personal Information. LS00-3NumberedParaHow we share Personal Information with other parties LS00-99H2We may share your Personal Information with the following persons, or classes of persons. LS00-3NumberedParaService providers under contract who help with our business operations such as fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, and technology services.
LS00-4SubParaAlphaCompanies that we plan to merge with or be acquired by.
Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your Personal Information. If your Personal Information could be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice. LS00-4SubParaAlphaLaw enforcement, government officials, or other third parties pursuant to subpoena, court order, or other legal process or requirements applicable to Majestri Pty Ltd or one of its affiliates.
LS00-4SubParaAlphaTo law enforcement agencies, or contracted investigators, when we believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of Personal Information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms and Conditions. LS00-4SubParaAlphaOther third parties with your consent or direction to do so. LS00-4SubParaAlphaPlease note that these third parties may be in other countries where the laws on processing Personal Information may be less stringent than in your country. However, we will take reasonable steps to ensure the third parties do not breach the Australian Privacy Principles in relation to the Personal Information. LS00-3NumberedParaMajestri Pty Ltd will not sell or rent any of your Personal Information to third parties.
LS00-3NumberedParaIf you create an account, take membership on, or transact directly on a third party website or via a third party application, any information that you enter on that website or application will likely be shared with the owner of that website or application.
These sites are governed by their own privacy policies and terms and conditions and you are encouraged to review their privacy policies before providing them with Personal Information.
Majestri Pty Ltd is not responsible for the content or information practices of third parties. LS00-3NumberedParaHow you can access or change your Personal Information LS00-99H2You can review and edit your Personal Information by logging into the Majestri Website profile settings page; or otherwise by contacting our Privacy Officer at support@majestri.com.au. LS00-3NumberedParaHow you can contact us about privacy questions LS00-99H2If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact us by email at support@majestri.com.au. If you have a privacy complaint, you should report it by emailing us at support@majestri.com.au. LS00-3NumberedParaHandling your complaints LS00-99H2We aim to: LS00-3NumberedParaAcknowledge receipt of all complaints within 5 business days; and LS00-4SubParaAlphaResolve all complaints within 60 days, however, this may not be possible in all circumstances. LS00-4SubParaAlphaWhere we cannot resolve a complaint within 60 days, we will notify you of the reason for the delay as well as an indication of when we expect to resolve the complaint. LS00-3NumberedPara
The end.
